davyjones.net 2006-10-19

# DavyJones.net User Agreement and Privacy Policy

We have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our usage conditions and privacy policies for the DavyJones.net website.

## Terms of Use

DavyJones.net is accessible worldwide to anyone with Internet access. Use of DavyJones.net is subject to the terms and conditions of this statement and all applicable laws and regulations, including laws and regulations governing copyright and trademark. By visiting the site, you accept, without limitation or qualification, all of the terms and conditions as stated in this agreement. DavyJones.net reserves the right to change these terms and conditions at any time. The changes will appear on this screen. By visiting the site, you agree in advance to accept any changes.

Your use of DavyJones.net is at your own risk. Neither DavyJones.net nor any of its subsidiaries, divisions, affiliates, agents, representatives or licensors shall be liable to you or anyone else for any loss or injury or any direct, indirect, incidental, consequential, special, punitive or similar damages arising out of your access or use of, or your inability to access or use, the site and the information available on the site or arising out of any action taken in response to or as a result of any information available on the site. You hereby waive any and all claims against DavyJones.net and its subsidiaries, divisions, affiliates, agents, representatives and licensors arising out of your use of the site and the information available thereon.

## Terms of Copyright

The materials used and displayed on DavyJones.net , including but not limited to text, software, photographs, graphics, illustrations, artwork, video, music, sound, names, logos, trademarks and service marks, are the property of DavyJones.net or its affiliates or licensors and are protected by copyright, trademark and other laws. Any such content may be displayed solely for your personal, non-commercial use and you agree not to modify, reproduce, retransmit, distribute, disseminate, sell, publish, broadcast or circulate any such material without the expressed written permission of DavyJones.net or its affiliates.

## Information and Privacy Statement

**Web Hosting Logs**. As with most servers on the Internet, our servers automatically log visitor Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, which are used to help diagnose problems with servers and administer Web sites. These addresses are also used to gather broad demographic information, such as geographic regions and popular Internet Service Providers (ISPs) for the purpose of creating content and information that appeals to our customers.

**Links to other Websites**. This site may contain links to other sites. DavyJones.net is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**PayPal Shopping Cart**. We utilize the PayPal shopping cart, which resides at the PayPal website, for products sold from our online store. Establishing a PayPal account is not required to purchase, and PayPal accounts are initiated and maintained by PayPal members at the PayPal website, and are not subject to our access or control. When a customer places an order through our PayPal shopping cart, we receive notice of the purchase by email from PayPal containing the following personally identifying information which we use to communicate with and ship merchandise to customers:

    * Name
    * Street Address, City, State, Zip Code, Country
    * Email address

This information is not stored on our website, and thus we provide no method of updating customers' personal and identifying information on our website. We do, however, maintain the confidentiality of this information to the best of our ability, and do not sell, share, or trade this information with any third parties in any way.

Contacting the Web Site. If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us. 

Effective as of July 27, 2004
